Totally positioning a person,
right?
And today is the fifty-fifth.
Fulfilling requests,
today I will invest in my style.
Come with me rascal.
I can have this size,
this look,
but in my size
changes a lot huh?
Oh my God from heaven.
I'm really going to wear that clothes here,
right?
Brother I'm tuned that some places you need to change
your position depending on what you want.
But the question I have to ask you is are you doing this
because you want to or just to try to get accepted?
You know the great freedom of people today,
in reality it's not even financial,
it's them being themselves.
It's on,
it doesn't sell authenticity for any price.
I believe the more authenticity you put in,
the more you strengthen your brand.
Cayon.
But you spent all day in the rain yesterday trying to sell your
project and nobody listened to you for your investment.
What if the message isn't coming?
Maybe it's not your style,
man.
And yes,
the strategy you're using is investing too much in my investment,
in my positioning and you don't have any content at all.
There are a lot of people with the same clothes and an empty mentality.
Connected guy that sometimes it can have a very good transformation
for someone else's business,
but sometimes it lacked a strategy that makes the business different.
The point is,
you don't have to fit in a box,
either a box,
and through that I think I had a business idea.
Damn fire in the playground.
I need to wear it my style now.
This is where there was about half an hour,
then I said I was going to invest in my style bro,
I took 1 sock there.
Basic gray and that's us.
I'll tell you that idea later it's valid until tomorrow.